National American Woman Suffrage Association Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
National American Woman Suffrage Association Records 1839-1961 1890-1930
MSS34132
National American Woman Suffrage Association
26,700 items
98 containers plus 1 oversize
39.2 linear feet
73 microfilm reels
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Founded in 1890 by the merger of the National Woman Suffrage Association and the American Woman Suffrage Association. Records comprising correspondence, a subject file relating chiefly to state and local suffrage organizations and leaders in the movement, scrapbooks prepared by Ida Porter Boyer documenting activities in the women's rights movement (1893-1912), and miscellaneous printed matter.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Boyer, Ida Porter, 1859-1952.; Fawcett, Millicent Garrett, Dame, 1847-1929--Correspondence.; Foster, Abby Kelley, 1811-1887--Correspondence.; Gardener, Helen H. (Helen Hamilton), 1853-1925--Correspondence.; Garrison, William Lloyd, 1805-1879--Correspondence.; Grimké, Sarah Moore, 1792-1873--Correspondence.; Harper, Ida Husted, 1851-1931--Correspondence.; Hay, Mary Garrett, 1857-1928--Correspondence.; Howe, Julia Ward, 1819-1910--Correspondence.; Kelley, Florence, 1859-1932--Correspondence.; La Follette, Belle Case, 1859-1931--Correspondence.; Livermore, Mary A. (Mary Ashton), 1820-1905--Correspondence.; Mott, Lucretia, 1793-1880--Correspondence.; Pankhurst, E. Sylvia (Estelle Sylvia), 1882-1960--Correspondence.; Park, Maud Wood, 1871-1955--Correspondence.; Peck, Mary Gray, 1867?-1957--Correspondence.; Rankin, Jeannette, 1880-1973--Correspondence.; Schwimmer, Rosika, 1877-1948--Correspondence.; Shaw, Anna Howard, 1847-1919--Correspondence.; Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 1815-1902--Correspondence.; Willard, Emma, 1787-1870--Correspondence.
Organizations
American Woman Suffrage Association.; Library of Congress. Manuscript Division. Suffrage Archives. 1759-1961.; National American Woman Suffrage Association.; National Woman Suffrage Association (U.S.)
Subjects
Suffrage--United States.; Suffrage.; Women's rights--United States.; Women--Suffrage--United States.; Women--United States--Societies, etc.
Titles
National American Woman Suffrage Association Records at the Library of Congress
Acquisition Information
The records of the National American Woman Suffrage Association were given to the Library of Congress in 1961 by Edna Lamprey Stantial, archivist of the association.
Related Material
The National American Woman Suffrage Association (NAWSA) records are closely linked by provenance and subject matter with the Blackwell family papers and with the Carrie Chapman Catt papers. These three collections held by the Manuscript Division have been known collectively as the Suffrage Archives. Also related by provenance is the Library of the National American Woman Suffrage Association and its president Carrie Chapman Catt, a library of seven to eight hundred titles collected between 1890 and 1938 by members of NAWSA and donated to the Library of Congress Rare Book and Special Collections Division by Catt in 1938.
Access and Restrictions
The records of the National American Woman Suffrage Association are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Microfilm
A microfilm edition of these papers is available on seventy-three reels. Consult reference staff in the Manuscript Division concerning availability for purchase or interlibrary loan. To promote preservation of the originals, researchers are required to consult the microfilm edition.
Online Content
The records of the National American Woman Suffrage Association are available on the Library of Congress Web site at https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.mss/collmss.ms000083. To promote preservation of the originals, researchers are required to consult the online edition.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the National American Woman Suffrage Association (NAWSA), founded in 1890 by the merger of the National Woman Suffrage Association and the American Woman Suffrage Association, span the years from 1839 to 1961 but are most numerous for the period 1890-1930. These records document the organization's history and activities, and are organized into the following series: General Correspondence, Subject File, and Miscellany.
The General Correspondence series consists of correspondence with individual members and supporters of the association, and with its officials. The series also incorporates correspondence with related organizations, and with the Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and other units of NAWSA. The collection features letters from many of the leaders in the woman's rights movement, including pioneer figures such as Millicent Garrett Fawcett, Abby Kelley Foster, Helen H. Gardener, Sarah Moore Grimké, Julia Ward Howe, Florence Kelley, Mary Ashton Rice Livermore, Lucretia Mott, Anna Howard Shaw, Elizabeth Cady Stanton, and Emma Willard. More recent leaders are represented by Ida Husted Harper, Mary Garrett Hay, Belle Case La Follette, E. Sylvia Pankhurst, Maud Wood Park, Mary Gray Peck, Jeannette Rankin, and Rosika Schwimmer.
Other correspondents include prominent writers, reformers and political leaders such as Henry Ward Beecher, William Edgar Borah, Witter Bynner, W. H. Channing, Eugene V. Debs, Albert Einstein, Ralph Waldo Emerson, William Lloyd Garrison, William Dean Howells, Robert M. La Follette, Ben B. Lindsey, Upton Sinclair, Ainsworth Rand Spofford, Theodore Tilton, Oswald Garrison Villard, James Wolcott Wadsworth (1877-1952), Theodore Dwight Weld, and Woodrow Wilson.
The Subject File includes biographical information on some of the principal suffrage workers, a collection of antisuffrage literature, progress reports from state and local suffrage organizations affiliated with the National American Woman Suffrage Association, records relating to the work of the Congressional Union for Woman Suffrage, formed by the merger of NAWSA's Congressional Committee with the National Woman's Party in 1917, and litigation proceedings resulting from Mrs. Frank Leslie's bequest of one million dollars to the organization. The subject file includes important material on the official organ of the association, the Woman's Journal, 1907-1949. Among the printed items in the Miscellany series is a set of indexed scrapbooks prepared by Ida Porter Boyer which document activities in the woman's rights movement as reported in the nation's newspapers and periodicals during the years 1893-1912.
Organization of the Papers
The collection is arranged in three series:
General Correspondence, 1839-1961
Subject File, 1851-1953
Miscellany, 1890-1950
Container List
Microfilm edition available. Shelf no. 18,404
- General Correspondence, 1839-1961 (Box 1-36, Reel 1-24)
  Letters sent and received, with related material such as magazine articles, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and other printed matter, photographs, press releases, receipts, and telegrams.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Adadourian, Haig (Box 1, Reel 1)
  - Adadourian, Honora A.
  - Adams, Alva
  - Adams, Charles Follen
  - Adams, Ellen F.
  - Adamson, Ethel
  - Addams, Jane
  - Adkinson, Florence M.
  - Adkinson, June
  - Alabama suffrage associations
  - Alaska suffrage associations
  - Aldrich, Louisa G.
  - Algeo, Sara M.
    - 1911-1913
    - 1914-1915
    - 1916
    - 1917
    - 1918-1950
    - Undated (Box 2, Reel 1)
  - Allen, Corinne M.
  - Allen, Florence E.
  - Allen, Lucy E.
  - Allen, Marguerite L.
  - Allen, Mary W.
  - Allen, Viola
  - Alphonse, E. C.
  - American Association of University Women
  - American Press Association
  - American Purity Alliance
  - Ames, Charles G.
  - Ames, Isaac
  - Ames, Mary
  - Anderson, Elizabeth G.
  - Anderson, Frances
  - Anderson, Mary
  - Andrews, Esther M.
  - Andrews, Gertrude N.
  - Angell, George T.
  - Anthony, Elisabeth Lyell
  - Anthony, Lucy E.
  - Appel, Doris (Box 2, Reel 2)
  - Arkansas suffrage associations
  - Arnold, Leila
  - Ashby, Margery C.
  - Athol Public Library, Athol, Mass.
  - Atkinson, Mary C.
  - Atwood, Beth H.
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Avery, Rachel F.
  - Babcock, Maude R. (Box 3, Reel 2)
  - Bacon Archaeological Research
  - Bagley, Grace H.
  - Bailey, Hannah J.
  - Bailie, Helen T.
  - Bakeman, Robert A.
  - Baker, Fred
  - Baker, Rachel
  - Baker, S. Josephine
  - Balch, Emily G.
  - Baldwin, Roger
  - Baldwin, Thaddeus
  - Ball, Susan A.
  - Barber, Amzi L.
  - Barker, Esther
  - Barker, Mrs. H. M.
  - Barker, M.
  - Barnes, Mary A.
  - Barnum, Phineas T.
  - Barooshian, Stephen M.
  - Barrett, Kate W.
  - Barron, Jennie L.
  - Barrows, Esther
  - Barrows, Evelyn
  - Barrows, Isabel
  - Barrows, Mary L.
  - Bartelmez, Leila
  - Barth, Ramona S.
  - Bascom, Emma C.
  - Bascom, Rose
  - Bashford, J. W.
  - Bass, Mrs. George
  - Bates, Francis E.
  - Bates, John L.
  - Beard, Mary R.
  - Beatley, Margaret B.
  - Beck, Margaret G.
  - Bedig, B. G.
  - Beecher, Charles
  - Beecher, Henry Ward
  - Beeman family
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Bell, Helen
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2 (Box 3, Reel 3)
  - Belmont, Alva E.
  - Belote, T. T.
  - Benchley, Belle J.
  - Bennett, Sarah C.
  - Benton, Irene
  - Berkman, Edith
  - Betts, Mattie M.
  - Bicknell, Thomas W. (Box 4, Reel 3)
  - Bigelow, Cora
  - Bird, Anna C.
  - Bird, Charles S.
  - Bishop, Mrs. L. B.
  - Bittenbender, H. C.
  - Black, George A.
  - Blaisdell, Alice L.
  - Blake, Katherine D.
  - Blake, Lillie D.
  - Blanchard, Henry
  - Blankenburg, Lucretia L.
  - Blatch, Harriot S.
  - Blaunett, Anna H.
  - Bliven, Ella C.
  - Blodgett, Margaret P.
  - Blood, Charles W.
  - Bloor, Ella R.
  - Blyth, Edward K.
  - Boland, Esther F.
  - Bolles, Ellen M.
  - Boobar, Erma S.
  - Boole, Mary E.
  - Borah, William Edgar
  - Boston Evening Clinic and Hospital, Boston, Mass.
  - Bowditch, William I.
  - Bowen, Louise de Koven
  - Bowles, M. C.
  - Bowne, Kate M.
  - Bowyer, Sara A.
  - Boyer, Ida Porter
    - 1904-1933
    - 1934-1949
  - Boyer, Richard Porter
  - Boyer, Rita
  - Bradbury, Edwin P.
  - Bradwell, James B.
  - Bragdon, Elspeth
  - Brahany, Thomas W.
  - Brainard, J. S.
  - Brainerd, Eveline
  - Breckinridge, Sophonisba P.
  - Breshkovsky, Catherine (Box 5, Reel 4)
    - 1910
    - 1911, Jan.-May
    - 1911, June-Dec.
    - 1912
    - 1913, Feb.
    - 1913, Mar.
    - 1913, Apr.-July
    - 1913, Aug.-Oct.
    - 1913, Nov.-Dec.
    - 1914
    - 1915
    - 1916
    - 1917
    - 1918
    - 1919
    - 1920
    - 1921
    - 1922
    - 1923
    - 1924 (Box 6, Reel 4)
    - 1925
    - 1926
    - 1927
    - 1928-1929
    - 1930-1934
    - Copy of postals
    - Undated, 1 of 4
    - Undated, 2 of 4
    - Undated, 3 of 4
    - Undated, 4 of 4
  - Brin, Alexander (Box 7, Reel 4)
  - Brookline Equal Suffrage Association, Brookline, Mass.
  - Brooks, John G.
  - Browman, A. A.
  - Brown, Alice
  - Brown, Gertrude F.
  - Brown, Louise
  - Brown, Olympia
  - Browne, Annie Leigh
  - Brownlee, Jane (Box 7, Reel 5)
  - Bryan, William Jennings
  - Buffinton, Maude E.
  - Bulkley, Mary
  - Burdette, Clara B.
  - Burleigh, Celia
  - Burleigh, Florence
  - Burleigh, Gettie
  - Burnett, Constance B.
  - Burr, Frances E.
  - Burtt, Philomela
  - Bushee, Alice H.
  - Bushnell, Katharine C.
  - Business Committee, NAWSA
  - Butler, Harriet B. C.
  - Bynner, Witter
  - California suffrage associations
  - Callanan, M. C.
  - Campbell, George M.
  - Campbell, Isabella
  - Campbell, Jane
  - Campbell, Margaret W.
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Candler, John W.
  - Canfield, Mary G.
  - Cantrill, Ethel
  - Carter & Blood
  - Cattell, J. D.
  - Chaapel, Jay
  - Chace, Elizabeth B.
  - Chamberlain, D. H.
  - Champlin, Arthur B.
  - Chandler, William E.
  - Channing, Eva
  - Channing, W. H. (Box 8, Reel 5)
  - Chase, Alice B.
  - Chase, Alice P.
  - Chase, Mary N.
  - Cheever, Helen
  - Cheney, Ednah D.
  - Cherry, O. A.
  - Cheyney, Lucia Trent
  - Child, Lydia Maria
  - Child, Ruth L. S.
  - Churchill, Anna Q.
  - Churchill, Elizabeth K.
  - Clapp, Mrs. William C.
  - Clark, Gertrude P.
  - Clarke, Albert
  - Clarke, Edward P.
  - Clarke, James Freeman
  - Clarke, James W.
  - Clarke, Lilian F.
  - Clary, Fannie J.
  - Clay, J. Inez
  - Clay, Laura
  - Clay, Mary B.
  - Clement, Edward H.
  - Clinton, S. H. M.
  - Cobb, M. H.
  - Cobbe, Frances P.
  - Cochran, C. Euphemia
  - Codman, C. H.
  - Codman, John S.
  - Coe, Evelyn P.
  - Coe, M. R.
  - Coffin, A. B.
  - Colby, Clara B.
  - Cole, Miriam M.
  - Coleman, George W.
  - College Equal Suffrage League
  - Collins, Emily P.
  - Collins, J. A.
  - Colorado suffrage associations (Box 8, Reel 6)
  - Colquitt, O. B.
  - Connecticut suffrage associations
  - Conover, Charlotte R.
  - Cook, Ellen M.
  - Cook, Lizzie M.
  - Copeland, Lillian
  - Corbin, Caroline F.
  - Cornell, Alonzo B.
  - Costigan, Mabel C. (Box 9, Reel 6)
  - Covall, Mary Ann
  - Crane, Caroline B.
  - Crane, S. A.
  - Crooker, J. H.
  - Crosby, W. C.
  - Crossett, Ella H.
  - Crowell, Grace N.
  - Crowley, Teresa A.
  - Cunningham, Minnie F.
  - Curtis, George W.
  - Cushier, E. M.
  - Cushing, Thomas
  - Cutler, Hannah M. Tracy
  - Dall, Caroline H.
  - Dally, Marion L.
  - Daly, Alice L.
  - Dame, Lydia M.
  - Dana, Henry W. L.
  - Danforth, Pitt W.
  - Daniel, Annie S.
  - Danielson, Rosamond
  - Dargan, Olive Tilford
    - 1913
    - 1914-1922
    - 1924-1950
    - Undated
  - Davis, A. B.
  - Davis, Andrew J.
  - Davis, M. B.
  - Davis, Paulina W.
  - Day, D.
  - Decker, Jane E. (Box 10, Reel 6)
  - Delano, Julia
  - Delaware suffrage associations
  - Dellhora, Guillermo
  - Dennett, Mary Ware
  - DeNormandie, Alice
  - Dewey, E. M.
  - Dewson, Mary W.
  - Dey, Haryot H.
  - Diaz, Abby Morton (Box 10, Reel 7)
  - Dickinson, Anna E.
  - Dietrich, Irene E.
  - Dietrich, Margretta
  - Dietrick, Ellen B.
  - Dillon, Mary E.
  - Diran, A.
  - Diran, Mary
  - Diran, Nazeli H.
  - Diran, Varteni B.
  - Directors, Board of, NAWSA
  - District of Columbia suffrage associations
  - Dock, Lavinia L.
  - Dole, Charles F.
  - Dolle, Lillian S.
  - Donaldson, Frank
  - Dorrance, C.
  - Douglass, Helen
  - Drake, Frances H.
  - Draper, E. S.
  - Draper, William S.
  - Drayton, Catherine
  - Driscoll, Mary E.
  - Duckering, Florence W.
  - Dudley, Helena S.
  - Dunham, Otis E.
  - Duniway, Abigail S.
  - Duniway, C. A.
  - Du Pont, Zara
  - Dwight, Minnie R.
  - Earle, Mary A.
  - Earle, S. H.
  - Eastman, Elaine G.
  - Eastman, Elizabeth
  - Eastman, Mary
  - Eddy, Eliza F.
  - Eddy, Sarah J.
  - Edgerton, Charles E. (Box 11, Reel 7)
  - Edwards, Marie S.
  - Eksergian, C.
  - Elder, William
  - Eldridge, Paul
  - Eliot, Charles W.
  - Eliot, Christopher R.
  - Eliot, Frederick M.
  - Elliott, Martha H.
  - Elliott, Maud Howe
  - Ellis, Henry D.
  - Ellis, R.
  - Ely, Robert E.
  - Embree, William D.
  - Emerson, Marjorie F.
  - Empire State Campaign Committee
  - Equal Rights
  - Evans, Elizabeth Glendower
  - Executive Council, NAWSA
  - Faithfull, Emily
  - Fall, Anna C.
  - Farnsworth, L.
  - Farnum, George R.
  - Fawcett, Millicent Garrett
  - Fearing, Mrs. George R.
  - Fernald, William F.
  - Fessenden, Elizabeth
  - Field, Edith M. J.
  - Fifield, Emily A.
  - Filene, Edward A.
  - Fish, W. H.
  - Fisk, Louisa H.
  - Fitzgerald, Susan W.
  - Flint, Elizabeth H.
  - Florida suffrage associations
  - Fogg, Olive C.
  - Foley, Margaret
  - Follin, M. D.
  - Foote, Katherine M.
  - Forbes, Rose D.
  - Ford, J. D. M.
  - Ford, Lewis
  - Forster, Rudolph
  - Foster, Abby Kelley
  - Foster, Alla W. (Box 11, Reel 8)
  - Foulke, William Dudley
  - Franklin, Lucy J.
  - Freeman, Elisabeth
    - 1913, June 7-July 12
    - 1913, July 17-July 28
    - 1913, July 30-Aug. 1
    - 1913, Aug. 12-Nov. 17 (Box 12, Reel 8)
    - 1913
  - Fuller, Berenice Morrison
  - Fuller, Harriet P.
  - Funk, Antoinette
  - Gabelle, James
  - Gage, Frances D.
  - Gage, Matilda J.
  - Gage, Portia
  - Gale, Zona
  - Gallinger, Jacob H.
  - Gallivan, James A.
  - Gallup, George B.
  - Gannett, Mrs. Lewis
  - Gardener, Helen H.
    - 1 of 3
    - 2 of 3
    - 3 of 3
  - Garrison, Charles
  - Garrison, Edith
  - Garrison, Eleanor
  - Garrison, Fanny
  - Garrison, Frank J.
  - Garrison, Marianne
  - Garrison, William Lloyd
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Garrison, William Lloyd, Jr.
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Garvin, Florence
  - Gates, Merrill
  - Gault, Bertha H.
  - Gawthorpe, Mary
  - Gay, S. H.
  - Gellhorn, Edna F.
  - Genthe, Martha K.
  - Genthe, Wilhelm
  - German Times
  - Geyer, Rose
  - Gillespie, Mabel
  - Gilman, Charlotte P.
  - Gilson, Sara S.
  - Gist, William H.
  - Gladstone, W.
  - Glazier, W. B.
  - Glick, Israel
  - Goddard, D. A.
  - Goldberg, Harriet
  - Goldberg, Isaac
  - Goldman, Emma (Box 13, Reel 8)
  - Goldstein, Fanny
  - Goodale, John H.
  - Goodridge, Benjamin A. (Box 13, Reel 9)
  - Goodridge, Julia W.
  - Goodwin, Angier L.
  - Gordon, Kate M.
  - Gorman, Thomas Y.
  - Graham, Marcus
  - Grant, W. T.
  - Graves, Anna M.
  - Greely, Ann F.
  - Greene, Caroline B.
  - Greenhalge, F. T.
  - Greenwood, Grace
  - Gregg, Richard B.
  - Grew, Mary
  - Grimké, Angelina
  - Grimké, Blanche S.
  - Grimké, S. S.
  - Grimké, Sarah Moore
  - Griswold, Howard
  - Grosser, Augusta D.
  - Grosser, Philip B.
  - Hagar, Louise
  - Haggart, Mary E.
  - Hagopian, Horhan
  - Hagopian, L. G.
  - Hall, F. Josephine
  - Hallet, Clara J.
  - Hamilton, Alice
  - Hamilton, John W.
  - Hamilton, Margaret V.
  - Hamilton, Marian S.
  - Hanaford, Phebe A.
  - Hansl, Eva
  - Harding, Florence M.
  - Harlow, William T.
  - Harmon, David P.
  - Harmon, Sidney
  - Harper, Ida Husted
  - Harris, E. P.
  - Harrison, Estelle
  - Hartman, Lewis O.
  - Hartshorne, Mrs. Edward Y.
  - Harvey, Paul
  - Haskell, L.
  - Haskell, Mehitable [Mehitabel?]
  - Hatch, Elizabeth J.
  - Hatch, Helen L.
  - Hauser, Elizabeth J.
  - Haven, G.
  - Hay, Mary Garrett (Box 14, Reel 9)
  - Haymaker, Catherine L.
  - Hazard, Rebecca N.
  - Hazlett, M. A.
  - Hazzard, Florence W.
  - Heacock, Annie
  - Heacock, Priscilla W.
  - Heath, Effie M.
  - Hebard, Grace R.
  - Heghinian, Garabed G.
  - Heming, Mrs. Charles E.
  - Henderson, Jessica
  - Henry, Alice
  - Henry, Edward
  - Hepburn, Katharine H.
  - Herbert, Rose
  - Herreshoff, Lewis
  - Higgins, Marion
  - Higginson, Mary T.
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth (Box 14, Reel 10)
  - Hildreth, S. F.
  - Hill, Charlotte L.
  - Hill, Helen
  - Hillard, Mary R.
  - Hitchcock, Daniel G.
  - Hoar, George F.
  - Holcombe, Carolyn C.
  - Holden, Cadge S.
  - Holland, J. G.
  - Hollis, Henry F.
  - Holmes, John Haynes
  - Holt, Erwin A.
  - Homer, Thomas J.
  - Hooker, Edith H.
  - Hooker, Isabella B. (Box 15, Reel 10)
  - Hooker, John
  - Hooper, Jessie
  - Hopkins, S. C.
  - Horton, Albert W.
  - Hosford, Frances J.
  - Hourwich, Isaac A.
  - Howard, Mrs. George
  - Howe, Julia Ward
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Howe, M. A. DeWolfe
  - Howe, Samuel G.
  - Howell, Mary S.
  - Howells, William Dean
  - Howland, Alice F.
  - Howland, Emily
  - Howland, Isabel
  - Hoyt, John W.
  - Huddleston, C. Roy
  - Hudson, E. O.
  - Hughes, Charles Evans
  - Hunt, Caroline L.
  - Hunt, Susan F.
  - Hunter, Arthur
  - Hunter, Mary Ashton Rice
  - Hunting, May A.
  - Huntington, Anna B.
  - Huntington, Ella M.
  - Husbands, Julia M.
  - Hussey, Cornelia C.
  - Hussey, Mary D.
  - Hutchins, Alice P.
  - Hutchinson, John
  - Hyndman, Mary P.
  - Idaho suffrage associations
  - Illinois suffrage associations
  - Indiana suffrage associations
  - Ingersoll, Henrietta
  - International Alliance of Women
  - International Woman Suffrage Alliance (Box 16, Reel 10)
    - 1913
    - 1920
    - 1921
    - 1922
    - 1923
    - 1924
    - 1925, 1 of 2
    - 1925, 2 of 2 (Box 16, Reel 11)
    - 1926
    - 1928
    - 1929
    - 1931
    - 1932
    - 1933
    - 1934
    - 1936
    - 1937
    - 1938-1939
    - 1941
    - 1942
    - 1943
    - 1945
    - 1946, 1 of 2
    - 1946, 2 of 2
    - 1947-1948
  - Iowa suffrage associations (Box 17, Reel 11)
  - Irwin, Inez H.
    - 1904-1929
    - 1932-1936
    - 1938-1943
    - 1944-1946
    - 1947-1960, undated
  - Jackson, Annie
  - Jackson, Francis
  - Jackson, Gardner
  - Jackson, Mercy B.
  - Jacobi, Mary P.
  - Jacobs, Aletta H.
  - Janney, Anne W.
  - Janney, Mrs. John J.
  - Janney, O. Edward
  - Janney, R. A. S.
  - Jarvis, Mary E.
  - Jeffrey, Jeannette A. S.
  - Jennings, Mary M.
  - Johns, J. B.
  - Johns, Laura M.
  - Johnson, Augusta B.
  - Johnson, Ethel M.
  - Johnson, H.
  - Johnson, Mrs. Lewis Jerome
  - Johnson, Oliver
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood
  - Johnson, Rowland
  - Johnson, Samuel
  - Johnston, Mary
  - Jones, A.
  - Jones, Benjamin S.
  - Jones, J. Elizabeth
  - Joslin, Rebecca R.
  - Joy, Charlotte A.
  - Kansas suffrage associations
  - Keating, Edward
  - Keith, Lucy E.
  - Keller, Helen
  - Kelley, Agnes L. (Box 18, Reel 11)
  - Kelley, Florence
  - Kelley, Marion B.
  - Kelly, Christina
  - Kelly, Howard A.
  - Kendrick, Ella B.
  - Kennicutt, Robert
  - Kenyon, Dorothy
  - Kerr, Laura
  - Kingman, J. W.
  - Kingman, Mrs. J. W.
  - Kingsbery, Laura
  - Kitchen, Sarah
  - Kleiber, Hans
  - Koehler, Mary Gray (Box 18, Reel 12)
  - La Croix, Eliza
  - Ladd, Mary H.
  - Ladd, William H.
  - Laddey, Clara S.
  - La Follette, Belle Case
  - La Follette, Fola
  - La Follette, Robert M.
  - Laidlaw, Harriet B.
  - Lakeman, Jane
  - Lakeman, Mary R.
  - Lane, Eliza
  - Larned, Augusta
  - Lathrop, Julia C.
  - Laughlin, Gail
  - Lawrence, Emmeline Pethick
  - Lawrence, F. W. Pethick
  - Leavitt, Ezekiel
  - Leavitt, Gertrude S.
  - Lee, Lucy M.
  - Lee, Mary
  - Lent, K. A.
  - Leonard, Florence P.
  - Leonard, Gertrude H.
  - Leslie, Mrs. Frank
  - Leslie Woman Suffrage Commission
    - 1 of 4
    - 2 of 4
    - 3 of 4
    - 4 of 4
  - Lesser, Alice P.
  - Lewis, Agnes B.
  - Lewis, Alfred B.
  - Lewis, Emily K.
  - Lewis, Graceanna
  - Lewis, Katherine B.
  - Lexow, Caroline
  - Lincoln Magazine
  - Lindsey, Ben B. (Box 19, Reel 12)
  - Lingenfelter, Corinne Coggeshall
  - Little, H. M.
  - Littman, Minna
  - Livermore, D. P.
  - Livermore, Mary Ashton Rice
    - 1869-1881
    - 1882-1892
    - 1893-1894
    - 1897-1898
    - 1899-1900
    - 1901
    - 1902-1903
  - Livingston, Deborah K.
  - Lloyd, Lola M.
  - Lloyd, Mercy
  - Lockwood, Belva A.
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr.
  - Loewenberg, Bert James
  - Loines, Hilda
  - Loines, Mary H.
  - London Mercury
  - Long, John D.
  - Longley, Elias
  - Longley, Margaret V.
  - Lounds, Thomas S.
  - Love, Alfred H.
  - Lovejoy, Esther P.
  - Lowell, Ettie L.
  - Luce, Allena
  - Luce, Gertrude R.
  - Ludington, Katharine
  - Ludlaw, R.
  - Luescher, Willard I.
  - Lund, Mrs. Haviland H.
  - Lunn, John W.
  - Lusignan, Guy de
  - Lutch, Albert M.
  - Luther, F. S.
  - Lutz, Alma
  - Lutz, Bertha
    - 1927-1935
    - 1936, Feb.-Apr.
    - 1936
    - 1937-1949, undated
  - McCausland, Elizabeth (Box 19, Reel 13)
  - McCleary, Helen C.
  - McClure, Grace
  - McCollum, Betsy P.
  - McCormick, Anne O'Hare
  - McCormick, Katharine D.
  - McCormick, Ruth Hanna
  - McCulloch, Catharine W. (Box 20, Reel 13)
  - McKay, Martha N.
  - McKim, John M.
  - Macmillan, C.
  - McNamara, J. B.
  - Maine suffrage associations
  - Mallory, Minnie T.
  - Marks, Jeannette
  - Marsh, Daniel L.
  - Massachusetts Consumers League
  - Massachusetts suffrage associations
  - Massachusetts suffrage associations, regarding John W. Weeks
  - Massachusetts Work Projects Administration
  - Mather, Alice Hyatt
  - May, Abby W.
  - May, Samuel, Jr.